LIZAMAURINE FORTOZO **S**TUDENT



Profile

I am a current sophomore at IUPUI pursuing Media Arts, with emphapsis in Digtal Storytelling. I have 5+ years of experience working with kids, from newborn to teenager. I am currently working in customer service at the Captial Grille of Indianapolis, to strength my communication, time management, and collaborative skills. Look foward to hearing back.

Contact



14413 Country Apple Ct Fishers, IN 46038



317-985-8067



Education

- Fishers High School (2013-2017)
- Indianapolis University-Purdue University Indianapolis (2017-Current) Pursuing a Bachelors in Media Arts and Science through the School of Technolgy, and a Minor in Media Studies

Work Experience

- Taco Bell (2015-2016) Cashier
- Kroger (2016-2017) Cashier
- Nanny/Babysitter (spring 2017-fall 2017) Cared for children newborn to teens
- Captial Grille (fall 2017-current) Host, Server Assistant, Food Runner

References

- Frances Burrows Manager at Capital Grille 317-640-2802
- Ruben Xochitlatoa Manager at Capital Grille 317-995-2811
- Melissa Turner Mother of 8 Children 317-460-0257

Skills

- Can speak English and Spanish fluently
- Proficient in the Adobe Cloud and Microsoft Office
- **Editoral Skills**
- Knowledgeable in CPR
- Educated on Early Child Development